One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, chaos!
Just when I was guarding the bridge with good intentions and encountered a malicious team, the mind in front of the screen thought I could survive? You are a dragon zodiac sign,
Give you two guns, how can you defend the Space Bridge against the malicious formation of the Anti-Bridge Defending Alliance?
The Bridge Guard Alliance greets you, Captain. Now the enemy has been completely angered by you.
Waiting to launch a fierce attack on you. Now you have to face the enemy.
Thirteen minutes of aggressive attack, defense of the bridge, and successful evacuation. Tuanzu, you have to be careful,
Enemies are very cunning and try to attack you through blue ramps and black doorways.
Although the enemy was outnumbered, we were supported by Hudson's Orion.
It was the ragtag group of Backhand Bridge Alliance who had to avoid Orion and head towards the East End Suspension Bridge.
Facing the enemy's offensive, you have a decisive command and deploy allies in advance to assist.
This time you will face more severe offensive challenges.
Because the enemy is afraid of being accidentally injured by his own people, he will not divide his troops for a sneak attack.
You don't have to worry about bullets coming from behind, shoot directly behind cover. Just finished deploying tactics,
The enemy opened the bridge. This is the position you are most familiar with and the position where you feel most secure.
Before the bridge is released, cruise missiles and Luna's probe ship are attacking you at the same time. You seize the opportunity,
Take advantage of the opponent's desire to grab information and attack, and take the initiative.
The enemy's attack is not as fierce as you think. You seize the opportunity and bring down the enemy. Subsequently,
You observe the other side of the bridge point.
Coming from the Deep Blue Shield, and Tuanzuo, you choose to use loitering bombs to collect information,
Enemies were also observed under the bridge. After observing the information, you choose to attack the enemy outcropping,
Take down two enemies approaching you. The dark blue shield is fully charged with your attack, and when changing bullets at the same time,
Observe a red wolf walking towards you behind a dark blue shield.
After reloading, you performed a killing spree on Red Wolf.
At the same time, your allies bring down Deep Blue, who has taken away the body. The Backhand Bridge Alliance did not appear again,
I was suppressed by your momentum of defeating more with less. Under your command, the enemy was defeated.
You have won a brief moment of safety. After our ally Silver Wings observed the information,
You choose to play the long game to catch the big fish and let the enemy come to the rescue.
But can we really catch another attack from the Backhand Bridge Alliance?
Thanks to your rich experience, the enemy in the group will not be able to withstand your counterattack.
Every time when they are about to attack, they will be defeated by you one by one.
You have a great match with your loitering bombs. Unfortunately, when you attack an enemy on one side,
The enemy on the other side blew your helmet off. This managed to piss you off. After repairing the helmet,
Like an angry lion, you have issued an expulsion order to these rabble who want to invade your territory.
They sealed the cigarette and wanted to save people, which is a good sign for you.
You and your allies cooperated to launch loitering bombs, successfully disrupting the enemy's attack rhythm.
This also puts the situation in your hands again. The enemy has broken your helmet again,
Now you were completely angry.
After knocking down several enemies, you choose to hand it over to your allies.
Go to the small bridge by yourself to complete the final counterattack against the enemy. A beautiful ambush, the enemy was completely stunned by you,
They had no idea where the bullets came from. You who came to Xiaoqiao,
It was also found that the number of enemies was also greatly reduced. It's up to you to fight back against the group of enemies attacking the bridge.
Best chance. So next, take away all these intruders.
After the enemy breaks through your armor and allies.
You realize this is the enemy's last resort. You choose to keep them alive while they are still alive,
Give them the final blow. Yes, that's right. You lead your allies to charge against the Backhand Knock Alliance,
These stinky fish and rotten shrimps are no match for you. Under a wave of fire suppression, you took away the last deep blue.
The League of Hand Knockers greets you. Ensemble.
You protected the bridge once again.